Ihinari Expedition
This is Mini Ogram Star Last Ihinari Talk Zanacho, please.
I'm Karen Tachibana and this is Keetaz.
I'm Karen Tachibana. I'm Kietazu. Nice to meet you.
Ihinari Explorers.
Today we are going to explore with these two.
What are we going to do today?
Today's exploration is
Let's try to spin the gacha-gacha at eBeans!
Yay!
Why? Why are you kneeling?
Well, I don't know if you two know this, but...
There are more than 1,000 machines in e-Beans.
A thousand?
No, no, no, no, it's not funny.
It's Sendai and Sendai...
That's great!
I was just getting into the swing of it.
I heard that there are more messengers than in Sendai.
I thought I'd have you spin it endlessly today.
Great!
Do you two like rumble?
I love it.
Yes, you do.
There are so many gachas in Sendai and beyond today.
I'm sure you'll find something you like and I'll introduce you to it.
I hope you enjoy your GACHA-GACHA as much as you can!
Yay! I'm so happy!
Let's move on to the GACHA-GACHA booth!
Yes! Ready!
Okay, here we are at the rumble shop on the first basement floor!
Yay!
First of all, here we are!
There are so many here!
There's quite a few here, but here's this 100-yen coin that Hikaru is holding right now.
I exchanged 100 yen coins.
You can use it and spin it as much as you like.
Well, you see, if you spin as much as you like, the good bins will get crushed.
So, I'm going to use this to spin as many times as you like.
I'd like to set a limit to the number of times you can spin the wheel, and if you're in a position to do so, you're allowed to spin the wheel one at a time. We decide each other's favorite one and then we have a showdown.
If you think that Hikaru is going to play animal games, you can predict that he's going to play animal games.
If Light pulls out an animal-based gacha, that's the end of today's gacha for Light.
If you keep this ng word, you can keep on pulling the gacha gacha forever.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get the most out of it, but I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get the most out of it.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good deal on the newest additions to your collection.
I'm sure you've guessed that I'm going to do this, haven't you?
Hikaru, please predict which gacha-gacha Karen is likely to win.
I see... I see.
Okay, now that we've made our predictions, let's start playing the gacha-gacha.
There's still a lot to do, Kazu.
What are you going to do? Are you going to do what you like?
Yes, but I still think life would be more fun if you chose to live doing what you like.
No, no, the comparison is too big
You're lumping life in with messing around.
So let's just take a wait-and-see approach and draw what we like.
Yeah, we have to have fun.
But I like queen samples.
I think I'll probably start with food.
I think that's expected.
No, no, no, no.
Animals?
Is there something you've been eyeing?
I've always wanted one of these.
This capsule gracie.
I'm looking for this Onkami.
Okay, what do you think? Orun-chan.
I'm thinking of pulling this one.
What do you think? Is it a good first shot?
I'm sure it's fine.
Is it a Psychic Spare?
Can I pull it?
Really?
I think I'm gonna go with this one.
Okay.
I want Onkami.
I'll pull it.
I got it in one shot.
I won it in one shot.
That's great!
Well, I'll put it together later.
It's so cute!
I'm so happy.
I'm here for tea.
I came to drink tea with this.
Oh, my God.
She's gonna love it.
You like it?
I'd pay 10,000 yen for it anyway.
That's nice.
You look cute today.
Yeah, you look cute today.
You're painting on a handkerchief?
Yeah, it's amazing.
What's that?
Go for it, Bunny.
Tama, did you put it in?
Tama, I got it.
You want to try arranging it?
I'm waiting, I'm waiting.I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
Waiting. Waiting.
I'm waiting.
Is this it?
I'm gonna start with a four-letter word.
You want to put this in?
What, is it a glitch? Or is it a glitch? Which one?
Glitch? Or non-powered? Which one?
Oh, it's a glitch.
Oh, my God.
Okay, I'll open it.
Can you fix it?
Yes, sir.
Got it.
Okay.
1,000 yen handkerchief.
Cute! A thousand-yen handkerchief! Yay!
Then we're both done. So cute!
Karen, Capsule Grasshopper!
Capsule Grasshopper's wolf! Yes, I'm happy!
Let's start with this one.
Angel Bird, you taught her.
Of course. Of course.
If you fail, it's the end.
The result of the first round of KAREN's game...
Safe!
Yay!
Isn't it funny?
We want to do it together, don't we?
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Next is Hikaru-san's 1,000 yen bill handkerchief.
I can really see it.
It's really rich!
But the "1,000 yen" part is a little impatient.
It's not a 10,000 yen bill.
That's nice.
Cute!
Interesting and funny!
Hikaru-san's bill handkerchief gacha gacha gacha
That's it.
Thank you for watching!
You are safe!
Congratulations!
You both cleared the first round.
What was your guess, Shimin?
I guessed cute.
Cute, but...
It's cute, but...
It's a story.
We're both safe.
I'd like to go to the second round.
Okay.
Ah.
Oh, I see. Let's get the small fry.
Have you decided on this one yet?
I'm thinking of doing it.
This way.
What's this?
I think I'd like it.
I've always wanted one, but they're too expensive.
It's a big one.
So I'd like to pass it around.
It's so cute.
Like the correction fluid.
It's all so cute.
What are you after?
This pink correction fluid.
I think I want all of them.
I feel sorry for this one.
They say you can take it out of the box.
Let's go.
Invisible.
It's cute.
What is it?
Lassion.
Oh, this.
It's cute.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
I'm pretty.
I'm cute.
I just found it.
I'm in love all of a sudden.
A fluffy stuffed ham and tart.
Tart or good night tart
Don't ignore Ham.
It's just the two of us.
Tart's the one who's always pulling the wool over my eyes.
You'd rather have Tart, wouldn't you?
I wish I could.
How's your pull, Karusan?
Tart.
Tart?
That's a ham!
Stop acting like you've never pulled a ham before.
Ham's cute.
The results of the second round are in.Results of the Second Round
From Karen.
Bung.
She's so cute.
Here we go.
I'd like to announce the NG word.
Please.
Second round.
Safe.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm happy
Food!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
I eat boom food once in a while.
Every once in a while.
Don't thunk it, guys.
Like chalk.
I used to eat chalk.
I thought they were supposed to be green.
I guess it's safe.
Safe in the common sense of the word.
And...
Pam.
This is NG.
Lard.
Safe.
I'm guessing it's the cartoon type.
That's right.
It hasn't been animated yet.
Not yet.
So, both of you have cleared the second round.
There's more to come.
Yay!
Let's do turn 3.
Come on, it's turn three.
That's right.
You'd be surprised what you can get away with.
Is that a no-no?
Then I want to go for it.
What? I didn't know there were any left.
Here it is.
I didn't do it because I like to eat in the food zone, and I thought I'd be targeted.
Maybe I should do it.
A miniature collection of small souvenirs.
That's right.
I have jaga pokkuru.
But they're all cute.
Food.
I don't know... but is it cute?
I don't know what to say.
I'll have this one then.
Here you go.
What is it? What is it? What's this?
What? What is it? Peanuts?
That's so cute!
Is it a peanut thing?
Peanut things?
Oh, my God, it's so cute! You'd love it!
Oh, my God! It's so cute!
Why are they vacuum-packed like this?
The back is amazing!
It's real! It's written on the back!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God! It's so cute!
Thank you!
That's great!
It's so cute!
Oh! There you go!
No way!
Ham!
Poor Ham!
I want Ham!
Ham misses you!
There's a ham over there!
Oh, yeah?
She said, "Please!"
Dad: "I see you have this pattern, you make some of the same ones twice in a row."
Daughter "Please!"
Dad "Oh!
Can you tell by the color?
I've seen it before.
But not?
It's a tart.
It is a tart.
The tart is about to be invaded by fans.
The color.
The third round of NG words
I'm going to announce the third round of NG words.
First of all, Karen, what is this?
It's peanuts.
Just to confirm...
What kind of mess are you into, Karen?
Cute!
Ms. Karen.
Three rounds.
Failed.
Not cute.
When I asked her how many times she said
He said she's cute, cute, cute.She said he's cute and adorable.
Wait, it's not cute.
I thought it was food.
It's food.
It is food, but...
But they're making it cute.
And I made sure of it, didn't I?
I did
Before the announcement
I want to go a little further
Once it's a failure, then let's make it a failure.
So I thought, why don't you just say it with food?
I knew it was time for food.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it.
I see.
Okay, so... times, Hikaru.
Pam.
Pam?
Pam. From Pam.
Pam. - Pam.
Pagto, right? I'm not sure which way to look at it.
What's your verdict?
Safe.
And on the third turn, Hikaru...
He's eliminated.
That's the saddest thing I've heard in a while.
I know, right?
I'd still like to pull it, but I'm going to have to.
But there's over 1,000 units and I've only pulled three times.
I feel sorry for you.
I want to pull it.
Then do your best imitation of Tarte.
I'm going to ask you to put Tart in front of your face.
Imitate what you think Tart would say.
I'm going to say something like...
And then Karen's imitation of Tarte.
Three, two, one, please.
I love sweet things.
I'm Sango.
Yes, ma'am.
Resurrection.
It was a little different. Yay!
She's much prettier.
What's that?
She's hot.
How was it?
You can say "Ilay" and "hot shot".
Yes.
We're going to make a special comeback.
Yay!
Let's play four rounds.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Okay. Okay, we'll go for the fourth round.
Let's move around a bit.
From the 2nd floor, in front of the free hallway, to the restrooms.
Another great number.
There are a lot of them.
There is a lot of mess machines.
I'd like to start the fourth round there.
Is this it?
This is it.
What is this?
I don't know.
It looks like it could be a station attendant.
It's cute.
Maybe it's the name of the station.
Tokai Rin.
It's super normal.
That's the worst mistake you can make.
Some people call him Tokaibayashi.
Is this your name?
The station attendant's name badge.
So that's it?
That's amazing.
What is it?
Mr. Souma.
You can be Mr. Souma.
Karen Souma.
Karen Souma from now on.
This is it.
What's this?
I love fruit.
Which one do you want?
Strawberries.
Strawberries are so cute.
Strawberries! Strawberries!
Strawberry! That's great!
They're in the box! That's great!
Right on target! They're so cute!
That's great! It's in the box!
It's so cute! It's so cute!
It really is! It's so cute!
Here we go! Let's go!
Okay, I'd like to start with the NG announcement for turn 4!
Yay!
First, Karen's station attendant patch!
The result of this one is...
Out!
It's a story-type prediction!It's a neta-type forecast!
It's totally a story.
Karen, two outs in a row and you are done here!
Thank you for your hard work!
Weak!
But I did what I wanted!
But surely no regrets in life!
No regrets in life!
No regrets!
This is the end of Ms. Cullen.
But there's still Karen!
The NG word here is...
Safe!
Animal!
Is that it?
You thought you were going to get a ham and tart?
There were!
There were no three in a row!
Hikaru is a survivor.
Hikaru survived and continues the endless Gachaporn Challenge by himself!
Now that I'm a little alone
So we'll add one more NG word to the list.
Karen will give you two.
Please try to get through them!
The first one is this!
The second one is this!
Let's go for five rounds!
I've already decided!
This is it!
Sim-Chan!
Cinnamon and Sinchan collaboration!
What! I didn't know this existed!
Cinnamon and Sim-Chan!
It's a bibi!
Let's open it!
You're so cute!
Shinchang, you're not listening to me!
I want Sanrio!
I'm coming!
Ah! Sunflowers!
Oh!
Himawari is out!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
Happy?
Yes, I'm so happy!
Great collaboration!
So cute!
Okay, now, for turn five.
This way.
Sunflower
Collaboration by Himawari Nohara
Now for the results.
The result of turn 5 is
Safe!
Yay!
We did it!
That's great!
So we're on to the sixth round.
That's great. It's great that you made it this far.
Without getting hit once.
I wonder how far they'll go.
Indeed.
Well, now that we've cleared two NGs.
Three for the sixth round.
Oh, no.
I can do it. I'll be fine.
Ready? Okay.
Ready. Okay.
Let's go, Hikari-san.
Turn 6.
It's decided.
Patrol siren light.
I've been wondering about this from the beginning.
What color?
I want red, but there are only about three left.
Will it be red?
Oh! Blue!
Oh!
Whoa!
There's some kind of sound.
It's like an accidental light.
It's okay, it's okay. We can play Ultraman or something.
Color timer.
Oh, here it comes! The Light Police!
What are you policing?
Koginy Thief.
Kozhineny Thief, playback thief?
Not so much.
Now, let's announce the results of the sixth round.
The result of this round is...
Failed.
What?
Why?
It's a story, isn't it?
It's a tool.
We just saw the Hikaru Police.
It's a story.
No, no, no, no, no.
What?
Chan-chan, what are you going to do now that you're back on your own?
Wait a minute.Hey, hey, hey.
I don't bother because I'm bothered.
Please give up on this one. It's a story system.
Mr. Acar, I failed in the 6th round. But I enjoyed it a lot. That's great. Did you enjoy it?
Ibins had a lot of fun because there were so many of them. I heard he will be there all the time.
So, I got a lot of stuff.
That's great. You did it! A thousand-yen handkerchief.
It's true.
Ohkami.
Peanuts.
It's on the Soma Line.
How did you like it? Try it.
It's hard to find such a variety, so I did the whole picture.
It was a lot of fun.
I've always dreamed of doing all the gacha-gacha, so I'm really happy.
Next time, let's do it again, since we have more than 1,000 machines, let's do it after we try all kinds.
Please invite them. These two.
I'll think about it, because there are people who do only Pam and Tart.
I've been doing it privately in places where the cameras aren't rolling.
We have a lot to do, so please come.
I would love to have you all come too, so let's get together.
A lot.
You should go to Soma.
I hope you can pull a tart.
We hope you all come to E-Beads to mess around.
That's all for today's exploration. Thank you very much.
Next time explorer, next time explorer.